1。
1。
Why are you calling me Young Master?
لماذا تناديني السيد الشاب؟
Tang Wenqi,
تانغ وينكي ،
I think you're tired of living.
أعتقد أنك تعبت من العيش.
Young Master,
المعلم الصغير،
I'm going to
انا ذاهب الى
avenge E Fei today.
انتقام E Fei اليوم.
Do you dare to play another game with me?
هل تجرؤ على لعب لعبة أخرى معي؟
Today's training,
تدريب اليوم ،
I don't have time to play with you.
ليس لدي وقت للعب معك.
I want to report it to the mountain chief.
أريد أن أبلغ رئيس الجبل بذلك.
Let's see how he will deal with you.
دعونا نرى كيف سيتعامل معك.
Are you scared?
هل انت خائف؟
Okay,
تمام،
Are you trying to provoke me?
هل تحاول استفزازي؟
It's just
انه فقط
a good match. It's amazing.
مباراة جيدة.  شيء مذهل.
Nice ball.
كرة جميلة.
Again.
مرة أخرى.
Cool,
رائع،
How dare you hurt me?
كيف تجرؤ على إيذائي؟
What's wrong with hurting you?
ما الخطأ في إيذائك؟
If you don't respect him,
إذا كنت لا تحترمه ،
I'll rebel.
سأتمرد.
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
You.
أنت.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I'm leaving.
أنا راحل.
Fine. I told you
بخير.  أخبرتك
to train here,
للتدريب هنا ،
If you fish in troubled waters here,
إذا كنت تصطاد في المياه العكرة هنا ،
you'll be punished for running 50 laps around the school playground,
ستتم معاقبتك على الجري 50 لفة حول ملعب المدرسة ،
Well
حسنًا
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
Am I good?
هل انا بخير؟
Can't you get rid of
لا يمكنك التخلص من
your anger? You're so good.
غضبك  انت جيد جدا.
Don't you see that everyone has to run away?
ألا ترى أن الجميع يجب أن يهرب؟
I'm trying to attract fire for you, okay?
أحاول جذب النار من أجلك ، حسنًا؟
Why don't you know how to be grateful?
لماذا لا تعرف كيف تكون ممتنًا؟
Thank you so much.
شكراً جزيلاً.
I can't do it anymore.
لا أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك بعد الآن.
Boss,
رئيس،
why don't you run away?
لماذا لا تهرب
I won't run anymore.
لن أركض بعد الآن.
Run for me.
اركض من أجلي.
Really?
حقًا؟
Brother Qi,
الأخ تشي ،
what's wrong with Tang Wenqi?
ما هو الخطأ مع تانغ وينكي؟
What are you smoking
ماذا التدخين
in the morning? Go, go, go.
في الصباح؟  إذهب! إذهب! إذهب.
Brother Wu,
الأخ وو ،
did you go to the hot spring secretly?
هل ذهبت الى الينابيع الحارة سرا؟
It seems that they were right.
يبدو أنهم كانوا على حق.
they
هم
Now the whole Academy
الآن الأكاديمية كلها
knows about you and Feng Lingxiu.
يعرف عنك و Feng Lingxiu.
Me
أنا
I … I have nothing to do with Feng Lingxiu. I know
أنا ... ليس لدي أي علاقة بـ Feng Lingxiu.  أنا أعرف
that.
الذي - التي.
It seems Wen Qi knew that E Fei would target Wu Wancheng,
يبدو أن Wen Qi كان يعلم أن E Fei ستستهدف Wu Wancheng ،
so he made this decision.
لذلك اتخذ هذا القرار.
Attract the fire,
جذب النار
as long as you know it.
طالما أنك تعرف ذلك.
Ling Xiu also told me
قال لي لينغ زيو أيضا
to be careful with E Fei today,
لتوخي الحذر مع E Fei اليوم ،
But now it seems that
ولكن الآن يبدو أن
he didn't do anything about it.
لم يفعل أي شيء حيال ذلك.
Don't take it lightly.
لا تأخذ الأمر باستخفاف.
I'm afraid it's not that simple.
أخشى أن الأمر ليس بهذه البساطة.
It seems that this academy is not easy to be treated.
يبدو أن هذه الأكاديمية ليس من السهل التعامل معها.
Let's go back to modern times.
دعنا نعود إلى العصر الحديث.
How could it fail?
كيف يمكن أن تفشل؟
I did it according to the textbook.
لقد فعلت ذلك وفقًا للكتاب المدرسي.
I've failed twice.
لقد فشلت مرتين.
We're running out of materials.
المواد تنفد.
No way.
مستحيل.
I'm going to try again.
سأحاول مرة أخرى.
Success or failure depends on it.
النجاح أو الفشل يعتمد عليه.
Let's go home.
لنذهب إلى المنزل.
-Go home. -Go home.
-اذهب للمنزل.  -اذهب للمنزل.
That's me.
هذا أنا.
I only have one explosive left.
لم يتبق لدي سوى متفجر واحد.
You always
انت دائما
make people worry about you.
تجعل الناس يقلقون عليك.
You,
أنت،
Your butt is on fire.
مؤخرتك مشتعلة.
Water. Give me water.
ماء.  أعطني ماء.
I always thought that if I couldn't blow myself up in ancient times,
لطالما اعتقدت أنه إذا لم أستطع تفجير نفسي في العصور القديمة ،
I wouldn't blow myself up, right?
لن أفجر نفسي ، أليس كذلك؟
Can't I go back?
لا يمكنني العودة؟
Brother Wu,
الأخ وو ،
are you not feeling well?
هل ليس على ما يرام؟
can you hear me?
أيمكنك سماعي؟
Brother Wu,
الأخ وو ،
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
I just didn't accept the reality.
أنا فقط لم أقبل الواقع.
Accept the reality.
تقبل الحقيقة.
Brother Qi,
الأخ تشي ،
do you believe that people can change time?
هل تعتقد أن الناس يمكنهم تغيير الوقت؟
Anything is possible.
كل شيء ممكن.
Why don't you believe me?
لماذا لا تصدقني
If,
لو،
I mean if,
أعني إذا ،
You can change the time.
يمكنك تغيير الوقت.
When you go back to the past,
عندما تعود إلى الماضي ،
you find everything around you very interesting.
تجد كل شيء من حولك مثيرًا للاهتمام.
However,
لكن،
you can never go back to your present life.
لا يمكنك العودة إلى حياتك الحالية.
Will you be happy?
هل ستكون سعيدا؟
Then I might think,
ثم قد أفكر ،
why am I like this?
لماذا انا هكذا
Everything has a cause and effect.
كل شيء له سبب ونتيجة.
Since we're here,
بما أننا هنا ،
there must be a reason for us to be here.
يجب أن يكون هناك سبب لوجودنا هنا.
What it means to be here?
ماذا يعني أن تكون هنا؟
Yes.
نعم.
Since you can't choose,
بما أنك لا تستطيع الاختيار ،
you might as well try to find
قد تحاول العثور عليه أيضًا
your own meaning.
المعنى الخاص بك.
And you said
وأنت قلت
everything around you was fun, didn't you?
كل شيء من حولك كان ممتعًا ، أليس كذلك؟
That's right.
صحيح.
No, no,
لا لا،
no. I said it wasn't me,
لا.  قلت لم أكن أنا ،
And I said "if",
وقلت "إذا"
OK, OK.
حسنا حسنا.
Come and
يأتي و
take a look at
نلقي نظرة على
the freshly baked meat buns.
كعك اللحم الطازج.
Miss, take one.
آنسة ، خذ واحدة.
Okay Sir,
حسنا سيدي،
do you want an umbrella?
هل تريد مظلة
Dead face,
وجه ميت
let's go and have a look at that.
دعنا نذهب ونلقي نظرة على ذلك.
Boss,
رئيس،
it just came out.
خرج للتو.
-This is so nice. -Okay.
-هذا جميل جدا.  -تمام.
Get
يحصل
me one.
لي واحد.
Brother Qi, hurry up. Didn't you say
أخي تشي ، أسرع.  لم تقل
you would take me shopping?
هل ستأخذني للتسوق؟
Why is it so slow?
لماذا هو بطيء جدا؟
Brother Wu,
الأخ وو ،
we've already visited five streets in half an hour.
لقد قمنا بالفعل بزيارة خمسة شوارع في نصف ساعة.
Why don't we sit down and rest before we leave.
لماذا لا نجلس ونرتاح قبل أن نغادر.
Young man,
شاب،
you have to be energetic,
يجب أن تكون نشيطًا ،
Let's head to the next street.
دعنا نتوجه إلى الشارع التالي.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Nice sachet.
كيس جميل.
Isn't this Mr. Yanxi, Tang Wenqi?
أليس هذا السيد يانشي ، تانغ وينكي؟
Why are you here again?
لماذا انت هنا مرة اخرى؟
Are you stalking me?
أنت المطاردة لي؟
Why would I follow you?
لماذا أتبعك؟
Brother Qi and I.
الأخ تشي وأنا.
I went shopping with Brother Qi,
ذهبت للتسوق مع Brother Qi ،
but he's too slow to catch up.
لكنه بطيء جدًا في اللحاق بالركب.
But you,
لكنك،
what are you doing here without class?
ماذا تفعل هنا بدون صف؟
It's none of your business. You can just stay here
هذا ليس من شأنك.  يمكنك فقط البقاء هنا
if you have nothing to do.
إذا لم يكن لديك ما تفعله.
Leave me alone.
اتركني وحدي.
Mr. Tang seems to be doing business,
يبدو أن السيد تانغ يقوم بأعمال تجارية ،
but the degree of hoarding of the goods,
لكن درجة اكتناز البضائع ،
This business is not easy to do.
هذا العمل ليس من السهل القيام به.
Here it is,
ها هو،
Brother Wu.
الأخ وو.
I didn't expect you to run so fast with your short legs.
لم أكن أتوقع منك الركض بهذه السرعة بساقيك القصيرة.
Wen Qi,
وين تشي ،
why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Where is Mr. Tang?
أين السيد تانغ؟
Doing business here,
ممارسة الأعمال التجارية هنا ،
Tang Wenqi,
تانغ وينكي ،
I have an idea,
لدي فكرة
I can make all your goods sold out instantly.
يمكنني بيع جميع البضائع الخاصة بك على الفور.
Believe it or not?
صدق او لا تصدق؟
Are you serious?
هل أنت جاد؟
Of course,
بالطبع،
I happen to be free today,
تصادف أن أكون حرًا اليوم ،
I'll help you then.
سأساعدك بعد ذلك.
I'm afraid you're not bragging.
أخشى أنك لا تتفاخر.
Why should I brag?
لماذا علي التباهي؟
But what about this?
لكن ماذا عن هذا؟
It needs the three of us to do it together.
يحتاج نحن الثلاثة للقيام بذلك معًا.
No way.
مستحيل.
I'm sure it will be exposed.
أنا متأكد من أنه سيتعرض.
Don't talk nonsense if you want to make money.
لا تتحدث عن هراء إذا كنت تريد كسب المال.
Let's get started when you're ready.
لنبدأ عندما تكون جاهزًا.
How about this
وماذا عن هذا
Is it really good?
هل هي حقا جيدة؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
Everyone is here.
الجميع هنا.
Let's take a walk and have a look.
دعونا نتمشى ونلقي نظرة.
Handmade smart toys are the best choice
الألعاب الذكية المصنوعة يدويًا هي الخيار الأفضل
for friends and family to send to children,
للأصدقاء والعائلة لإرسالها إلى الأطفال ،
I only need 50 cents each today.
أنا بحاجة فقط إلى 50 سنتًا لكل يوم.
Don't miss it.
لا تفوتها.